Absolutely. Sir, I'll let you know
as soon as I know anything.
Not at all. It's... It's my pleasure.
- Crap.
- Director?
Bertram wants regular updates. Somebody
involved in this case must be connected.
Well, maybe we'll get lucky, catch a dunk.
- We're due an easy one.
- Ugh, you shouldn't have said that.
- Said what?
- "We're due an easy one".
Now we're jinxed.
Sorry.
Amber Sutherland, documentary filmmaker.
The house is a rental.
She's been in Crane Creek
for about two months
making a campaign video
for mayor Kenyon Bagshaw.
Isn't a campaign video overkill
for a small town mayor?
Well, Bagshaw's moving up.
He's running in a special election
for the house of representatives.
Surprise. Connected.
Agent Lisbon? Chief Arnold Nail,
Crane Creek P.D.
My men responded to a shots-fired
call last night, found the body.
- Agent Cho, Agent Rigsby.
- Men.
Did your men search the area?
We found a .38 in a trash can
down the street.
Serial number shows it reported stolen
from a man one town over
about a year ago.
- We're gonna need that.
- Got it.
And just so you know, I get it.
CBI's in charge.
We're here to assist.
Thanks, chief.
We don't always get a welcome.
Well, I said I get it.
I didn't say I liked it.
Looks like the killer tossed the place.
Anything missing?
Apparently, Amber had a lotta
high-end video equipment.
There's no sign of it,
so we figure the killer took it.
Robbery gone bad?
No, there's a lot of other valuables
left behind.
Okay, get a list of what's missing
and call Jane and ask him
why he isn't here already.
Patrick Jane, CBI.
I'm on the way to a crime scene.
Do you know how fast
you were going, sir?
Do I get a prize if I guess correctly?
13 miles per hour
over the posted speed limit.
I need your license
and proof of insurance.
I'd love to, but, uh, we got
a murder to solve.
Evidence degrading,
killers perfecting their alibis.
First 48 hours...
You know that, right?
License and proof of insurance.
I mean, is this really necessary?
Aren't we all part of the Justice League?
Do you think Aquaman
would give Batman a ticket?
Just consider that.
Step out of the car.
There's no sign of a struggle.
She probably knew the killer.
But if it was personal,
why take her video equipment?
Agent Lisbon, we might have something.
One of my officers is engaged
in a pursuit off a traffic stop.
Driver was acting crazy.
- Could be our guy.
- Don't say a word.
Vehicle is a blue Citroen,
about 30 years old
California plates.
See what you did?
"Pull over!"
- Morning, Lisbon.
- Freeze! Let me see your hands!
Did I miss anything?
Agent, I'm not opposed to extending
professional courtesy
but your man ignored a reasonable request
from my officer and fled.
- He will pay the ticket.
- Meh.
Speed traps. Legalized extortion.
You want people to slow down?
Park out in the open,
where they can see you.
But no, you lay in wait
like thieves in the night.
- He will pay the ticket today.
- I'm not gonna pay it.
- Jane! Stop... stop that.
- I won't pay it. I'm not paying it.
Extortionist.
If Mr. Jane will go to City Hall
and settle this today
- we can move on.
- Thank you.
- I'd like an apology.
- Oh, really?
Dream bigger, pal.
You're not gonna get one from me.
I said we'd move on.
Yes, we're moving on.
Don't know why you were in such
an all-fired hurry to get here.
I'll tell you who killed that woman.
Who's that?
Local scumbag
named Ronald Crosswhite.
Killed his wife two years ago.
He was indicted for murdering his wife.
- Oh, he did it, all right.
- Sergeant Rowley!
Why isn't he in prison?
There was a... screw-up.
Evidentiary paperwork got filed late.
Judge excluded some security footage.
Critical evidence.
Crosswhite walked.
Aha.
And you're the one that screwed up.
That's why you can't stop looking
at that poor woman's body
because you feel responsible.
Also explains why
when there's a murder in town
you're out working the speed trap.
- You smart-ass.
- Stand down. Now.
Yeah.
Looks like we both have a little problem
controlling our underlings.
- Underling?
- Even if Crosswhite did kill his wife
what does that have to do
with Amber Sutherland?
Saw the two of 'em together
day before yesterday.
Now she's dead.
No way that's a coincidence.
Underling? Really?
Lisbon, would you explain
to this man...
- You need to stop.
- I'm... I'm a consultant.
- He's a consultant.
- I'm not below or above.
- I am to the side.
- That's enough.
Ginger Crosswhite was 31.
Worked at City Hall, DMV clerk.
Shot and killed in their living room
two years ago.
The D.A. claimed Crosswhite
did it for insurance money.
He had an upholstery shop
that was struggling.
- And he walked?
- "Well, Crosswhite claimed"
"he came home from a drive
and found the body."
"A security camera image
showed him arriving home"
"an hour before he said he got there.
Destroyed his alibi."
"But sergeant Rowley missed
the deadline"
"to file the search warrant"
the judge excluded it,
and the case collapsed.
"Good work."
The mayor's wife is coming in
to the office.
Her name's Jessica Bagshaw.
She was supervising
Amber Sutherland's video work.
- I'll get her statement.
- "Okay. Be careful."
They have a lotta pull.
Teresa Lisbon,
toughest gal west of the Pecos
and you're scared of a small town
mayor and his wife.
Yeah?
Mr. Crosswhite, we're with the CBI.
- I'm Agent Teresa Lisbon.
- And I'm Patrick Jane.
We wanna ask you some questions
about Amber Sutherland.
Tom Rowley tell you about me?
Yes, he did.
That's my buddy Tom.
Can we come in?
How did you know Amber?
She, um...
She was filming me for a documentary.
The one about the mayor?
No, this was about my wife's death.
What are you doing?
Your wife looked lovely.
She had a very gentle face.
Put that down.
- Why?
- Just put it down.
Fair enough.
So Amber was making
a documentary about you?
Yeah. She... she did
a couple interviews.
She said she'd need
to, to raise money to finish it.
That must have been nice for you...
Tell your side to Amber.
You have no idea.
The man who killed my wife
is still out there.
But everyone in town
thinks I'm the killer.
It's, it's around me all the time.
It's like being underwater.
Feels like I can't breathe.
Well, if you didn't kill your wife,
what'd you do to her?
What?
You're the guiltiest-looking man
I've ever seen...
the theatrical squalor
forcing yourself to live
with the hatred of your neighbors.
If you didn't kill your wife,
then why the self-punishment?
You need to get out of here.
- Now.
- I have to agree.
Well, it's just an honest opinion.
A legit question, I'm doing my job.
Okay. Have a nice day.
It just seems insane...
Amber, gone.
She worked closely with you.
She was with us pretty much every day,
the last couple of weeks.
We'll need to speak with your husband,
Mayor Bagshaw.
Of course.
He's forging away on the campaign trail.
Elks clubs and coffee klatches.
Do you have any idea why someone
would wanna hurt Amber?
I can't imagine.
I mean, she was just...
- such a gentle soul.
- Okay.
You know anything about her
personal life? She seeing anybody?
Um, she had been on a few dates
with Zach Gladden.
He works at City Hall.
Was she close with anyone else?
Maybe someone with the campaign?
What is it that you're suggesting?
Nothing. Just...
- She was pretty and...
- And my husband is attractive
and charming and powerful.
Right?
Um, that's not what I was suggesting.
It's how rumors get started.
Um...
We have no interest
in having a pretty dead woman
attached to the campaign
if you get my drift, Agent?
Jessica.
Director Bertram.
Gale.
I was gonna come and see you
as soon as Agent Van Pelt
was done with me.
Agent, is she done?
Yes, sir.
Let's grab a cup of coffee.
Zach Gladden?
Tell us about Amber.
I don't know what to say.
She was cool.
God, that's lame.
She was from Los Angeles.
She was funny.
Really hard-working.
Tenacious.
We hear she was spending
some time with a man
named Ronald Crosswhite,
making a documentary?
He had been bugging her
since she got into town.
- Someone new to listen to his garbage.
- Garbage, is that how Amber saw it?
She said she was maintaining
her journalistic objectivity.
- Least until a couple of days ago.
- What happened?
She had an interview with him
and she said Crosswhite...
freaked out.
"You okay?"
"Yeah, I guess I'm just...
nervous, you know?"
"Let's start the questions."
Amber e-mailed this video
of the Crosswhite interview
to a producer friend in L.A.
a few days ago.
"Uh, just gotta jump right in, huh?"
"That's right. Your upholstery shop
was still open then."
- This the scary part?
- Wait.
- "There's a discrepancy about the time..."
- "There, there's no discrepancy."
"I've been looking at the security
camera footage..."
"D-d-don't tell me
about s-security footage."
"I was there when I said I was there."
"I came home, and my wife was dead.
I mean, don't... don't you get it?"
"There's, there's a real killer
out there somewhere."
- "Okay."
- "You said you believed me."
- "Calm down."
- "Were you lying?"
"Were you lying, too?
Are you one of them?"
- "Please calm down."
- "You one of the... I mean, what is..."
"Don't tell me to calm down!"
- "What is this? What is this, a set-up?
- "I just..."
- "Turn that off! Turn that off!"
- "Please..."
I'll get a warrant first thing
in the morning.
Get a list of Amber's missing equipment
and the serial numbers.
On it.
We're serving a warrant on Crosswhite
first thing in the morning
and you're coming with.
- Oh, sounds like fun.
- Don't worry.
We're dropping you at City Hall
so you can pay that speeding ticket.
I thought I made
my feelings very, uh, clear
- on that particular subject...
- Which is why I told chief Nail
if you don't pay it by noon tomorrow
he's free to get a bench warrant
for your arrest.
We're citizens, too.
We're not above the law.
Oh, well, thanks for that, Gandhi.
What I don't appreciate
is this cheap police state tactics.
Whatever works.
He's not here.
Warrant's good either way,
so, Cho, open the door.
Boss.
Found this in the garage.
The serial number matches
Amber's video equipment.
Call Van Pelt, have her put
a BOLO out on Crosswhite.
We need to bring him in.
- Thank you.
- "Good morning, Ms. Bagshaw."
Uh, excuse me, ma'am?
Um, I have a... I have a ticket.
Yes, see that clerk.
- So, you're the bagman.
- I guess.
Well, I would like to pay this ticket...
- But under protest.
- Nobody pays any other way.
Everybody stay where they are!
Everybody just stay
right where they are.
Now, you...
you get out there
and lock those front doors.
Try running, you'll have blood
on your hands. Go.
Okay. Okay, ev... everybody over there.
Over there by the window!
Get over there!
Stay there.
Guard, get over here.
Nobody move!
Oh, good. More guns.
Chief. What's going on?
Got a report
Crosswhite's in there with a gun.
- He's got hostages.
- We should secure the perimeter
and make contact with Crosswhite.
Well, thanks for the advice.
My people and I are gonna handle this.
You don't wanna start
a gunfight unless you need to.
We should get the information first.
If I'm hearing right
got a group of citizens in there
being threatened by a nut with a gun.
I don't need to know more than that.
Get over there!
Other... other side! Move!
Move!
I said move!
Shut up!
Okay. Three with me through
the front door.
The rest of you, hit the fire exit
round back.
You start a shooting gallery in there,
and people are gonna get killed.
- See you when we're done.
- CBI has authority here.
I will start arresting your men
and putting them in cuffs
if you don't stand down right now.
Chief, come on!
No, she's right.
CBI has jurisdiction...
for now.
You.
What's your name?
- Donna.
- Donna?
You look familiar. You a D.A.?
I'm a paralegal.
Jane, right?
CBI? What are you doing here?
Nothing. In fact, I was just...
I was just leaving.
I just heard on my police scanner
that you guys were looking to arrest me.
You people thought all along
that I killed Amber, didn't you?
What I thought is irrelevant now.
But how exactly is this gun-waving
supposed to establish your innocence?
Oh, I tried talking, it doesn't work.
Nobody listens.
Mind if I get that?
Hello?
Jane? Are you in City Hall?
Yes, unfortunately.
Is anybody hurt?
- Not mortally, yet.
- "What's going on?"
I'd love to chat with you, Lisbon,
but there's a man here
with a large gun,
who wants to talk to you.
Who's this?
Mr. Crosswhite, this is Agent Lisbon.
Let's just take it easy, okay?
You tell all those cops
to stay outta here.
I will. Why are you doing this,
Mr. Crosswhite?
Why, why am I doing this?
Why are you doing this?
I'm not doing anything
but talking to you.
What do you want?
I want a guarantee from the governor
and the State Attorney General
that I will not be prosecuted
for the death of Amber Sutherland.
We can talk about that.
And I want...
I want a new investigation
into my wife's death
"and I want the real killer found."
Do it now.
I had two months left on that plan.
May have found a way to hear
what's going on in there.
If we can patch into the main
switchboard for City Hall
we can turn any phone with a speaker
on it into a microphone.
Do it. Where's Nail?
He's taken over the cafe on the corner
for a command center.
Nail's tapped into the cameras
around City Hall.
- It's clever.
- Well, just trying to keep up.
It's the rear entrance to City Hall.
It's alarmed, but we can
disarm it from here.
We create a distraction
in front, send men in that way
and we'll minimize casualties.
It's... It's procedure to try and talk the
person who's taken the hostages out.
That's what we're gonna do.
Work with me, Lisbon.
We need a plan B.
Hell with that. Let's go.
We are not going in
unless Crosswhite fires first.
It's the safest path.
Unless you're the first hostage
Crosswhite decides to shoot.
Someone wanna tell me
what's going on?
Mayor Bagshaw, I'm Agent Lisbon
with the CBI.
Glad to hear it.
Nail, what's the plan?
Flashbangs through the side window
move in through the back,
take Crosswhite out.
- Get started on it.
- An assault like that
should be
the last resort, not the first.
A half-dozen people, including my wife
are in that building
with an armed lunatic.
I want them out.
I won't allow it.
CBI has the authority here.
Not anymore.
You're to work with us now.
If you don't believe me, talk to your boss.
I already did.
Lisbon, it's a matter of taking
the feelings of the locals into account.
Sir, this is a matter
of people not getting killed.
"You'll do your best
to prevent that, I trust."
I can't if I don't have the authority.
Now I know mayor Bagshaw
has a lot of influence, but...
No, there's no "but." All right?
Influence has influence.
I don't have to explain the politics
of this to you, do I?
Sir, this isn't about politics.
Everything's politics, Lisbon...
"One way or another."
Try persuasion. Works wonders.
What's the word?
- We're on our own.
- No, you don't want them going in.
We better do something.
They're saddling up.
Teresa, I know you're busy
but I'm babysitting a bunch
of reporters out there
who'll take a minute
whenever you've got one.
- Not now, Brenda.
- Fine. Uh, let me know when you can.
Wait a minute.
One. Now.
Great. Uh, anyone in particular?
Or should I just pick somebody?
Who do you think has the best access
to director Bertram?
We're human beings.
We have a right to use the bathroom.
There's one in the mayor's office
just right around that corner.
Hey, you're one of those cops
from outta town, right?
Uh, something like that, yeah.
Are you, like, working on a plan
to get us outta this?
Yes. Of course I am.
What are you doing?
Well, I'm... I'm thinking.
And waiting.
What are you, like, 5?
A little patience here.
They're gonna come in, you know.
And it's gonna get all shooty.
What's that gonna prove?
You know what?
Don't put this on me.
You're like all the rest of them.
You just decided I killed Amber.
S-same way they just decided
I killed my wife.
Well, more times than not
it is the husband that did it.
Yeah, well, I didn't.
There were break-ins
all around the neighborhood.
This was a robbery gone wrong.
I, I mean, just because some camera
says I was someplace when I wasn't.
No, they didn't even bother
to, to, to look into the robberies.
That's not true.
What did you say?
We looked into those break-ins.
It was just kids.
They turned on each other
the moment they got arrested.
- They're not killers.
- Donna...
You said you weren't
in the D.A.'s office.
No, I-I just said I was a paralegal.
Somebody killed my wife
and you were too busy
blaming me to catch them.
I-I-I'm sorry I said anything.
Please...
- Please don't shoot me.
- I'm not gonna shoot you. I...
Well, waving the gun in her face
is not a great idea.
Everybody just needs to shut up!
Look, I'm sorry, all right?
I'm sorry. Just please...
Just stop it.
I can help her.
Yeah, please.
It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
Just stand up. Breathe.
Just come over here and take a seat.
You know the breath is the switch
between the conscious
and the subconscious mind?
It's how one controls the other.
Just breathe.
Just breathe and relax.
Boss, we've tapped
into the phones at City Hall.
You're gonna wanna hear this.
- Lisbon.
- "Agent Lisbon."
"I, I just had a conversation
with... with a reporter from the Examiner."
He seemed to know a lot
about the situation in Crane Creek.
Now, I told him
that no matter what any
unnamed source might say
"CBI puts civilian safety first
and that we were not bowing"
"to local pressure to do otherwise."
I also told him
that authority in Crane Creek
resides with our head agent
in the field.
You.
"I've let Bagshaw and his chief
know that you're in charge."
Thank you, sir.
We'll discuss this again.
Good luck, Agent.
"In..."
"Out."
"That's good. In..."
"Letting yourself relax."
- "In and out. Just relaxing."
- What's he playing at?
- Sound like he's hypnotizing someone.
- "All the way."
- "Breathing in and out."
- Sir, we're ready to go.
Stand down. No assault
unless Crosswhite starts shooting.
- Agent Lisbon is in charge.
- This is ridiculous.
It's done.
Get back to your post.
"Relaxing your body..."
In...
And out.
Relaxing your body.
Let your eyes close.
That's good. That's good.
Your mind is in fight-or-flight mode.
There's nothing you can do
about that now
so just breathe in...
And out. Let it all fall away...
Fall into the floor.
Now, see yourself...
in a warm, safe place.
In... and out.
Now you're drifting.
Just drifting away.
Oh, my God!
- Oh, my God!
- They tried to kill me.
They tried to kill me.
Sons of bitches. They tried to kill me.
Close the blinds! Go!
Stand down!
Do not fire!
There he is.
Stop!
Stop! On the ground! Get on the ground!
Face down! Do it now!
Gimme your hands.
Well, what now?
You got me.
You could answer the phone.
Well, that's gonna make it
a little tricky to talk to 'em.
You're gonna talk to them.
I'll tell you what to say.
Okay.
I wanna take Donna with me.
She's hurt.
- She needs he...
- No.
We're gonna book you
for attempted murder.
Call your lawyer,
your union rep, I don't care.
I'm the reason
that Sutherland girl's dead.
- I wanted to make it right.
- Cho, get him outta here.
Come on.
- Boss...
- Yeah, I know. We lost the phones inside.
No, no, no.
It's Jane.
Don't shoot me.
Oh, Lisbon. Nice of you to show up.
Jane?
You know, you people oughta
be ashamed of yourselves.
Crosswhite hasn't shot anyone,
and you've shot Donna.
Is she all right?
Uh, for a shot person, yeah.
She's fine. It's just a graze.
Well, that was sergeant Rowley,
acting on his own.
Says you.
Look, Rowley's screwups
have cost me enough.
If it wasn't for him,
none of us would be here.
You're angry?
How do you think he feels?
Don't start to sympathize with him.
Who is Ronald Crosswhite?
He's a man that no one
has listened to
a man that has been abused
and pushed around.
It's hard not to sympathize
with the man. I do. I feel for him.
Damn it! This isn't a therapy session!
No, it's not. He says you got one hour
to put him in touch
with the governor
and the Attorney General
or he starts shooting hostages.
We'll get on that.
In the meantime could you ask him
to please release
the injured woman?
I never thought of that.
That's a great idea.
Not bad, CBI.
Tell me you didn't kill your wife.
I didn't kill my wife.
- You cheat on her?
- No.
You kept some secret from her.
No.
Yes. There's something.
You just thought about it.
What was it?
I...
I-I was a smoker.
She hated it.
You told her you quit, but you hadn't.
What did you do?
I...
went for long drives,
uh, clear my head...
Snuck a smoke, figured
what's the big deal, right?
That's what you were doing
the night she died.
Uh, I went for a drive,
I listened to some music
had a few smokes.
Came home, she was on the ground.
There was blood.
Put my hands to my face,
smelled the smoke on my fingers.
The last thing I told her was a lie.
And that's the guilt you carry around.
I shoulda been there.
I shoulda been there with her.
Have you ever considered that the killer
was waiting for you to leave?
Does that mean you believe me?
Sure, I guess.
But taking us hostage to prove it
is the dumbest idea you've ever had.
Donna...
The security camera footage
the big evidence
against Mr. Crosswhite
- who owned it?
- Uh, the el-electric company.
Perfect. And Rowley's mistake,
the one that got it thrown out...
Pretty stupid?
Hard to anticipate?
Of all the paperwork to forget
Rowley picked the worst.
That'll do.
Crosswhite, forget about the deadline.
I will tell you who murdered
your wife in 20 minutes.
- I just need three things.
- What?
First, Donna here is injured.
Let her go so she can be taken care of.
There's plenty of us here to shoot
if that's what you feel like doing.
Hey, wha...
Second, I need to go to the bathroom.
- Oh, me, too.
- And me.
- Fine.
- We all get to go to the bathroom.
And third, I need a pen
and some paper.
That's all you need to find
my wife's killer?
Yeah. You think the governor
can say that?
I doubt it.
Okay.
- "You okay to walk?"
- Oh, I'm fine. Fine.
- Tell Kenyon that I'm okay. Tell him...
- No messages.
Go ahead. Open her up.
Donna.
Donna. So brave. Oh, so...
- Ow! Ooh! Ooh. Ooh.
- Oh! Sorry. Forgot about your...
All right.
My bad.
Did Jane tell you to say anything?
Give you a message?
No. He just gave me a hug.
A hug?
Excuse me.
Jane sent us a note.
What's it say?
"Hey, everybody. Solved the case."
"Saw envelope on mayor's desk
left by Amber."
"Must be what the killer
was looking for."
"Can't get to it right now.
Yours truly, Jane."
"P.S: Lisbon, I'm not paying the ticket."
I don't know what the hell that means
but in ten minutes, the deadline's up.
Crosswhite said he's gonna start
shooting people.
Now, I don't care
what you have on Bertram.
If that psycho hurts my wife,
I will break you.
Your ball game, Lisbon.
So what happens now?
Well, what happens now is,
you and I take a walk outside.
- Are you crazy?
- Easy as pie.
- Uh, they'll shoot me.
- Not if I'm standing next to you.
I won't take that chance.
Well, you can take the walk outside
or you can stay in here and wait
for them to come in shooting.
Personally, I like your chances
out there.
I won't do it. I don't even know
why I'm listening to you.
Because I know what I'm talking about.
You're on the edge, and I've been there.
It's a dark and lonely place,
and I'm telling you
this is the way back.
And more than anything else,
I'm offering you what you want...
Your wife's killer
standing in front of you in chains.
Now, if you go out there
there's a chance that you will see that
but if you stay in here
you will probably die.
This is just a trick.
Oh, I wish. If this was a trick,
I'd be a lot more confident.
This is 60/40 at best.
But what's plan B, huh?
You coming?
Oh, that's a lotta guns.
Drop your weapon now!
You get Crosswhite.
We'll get the hostages out.
On your belly! Hands by your sides!
Spread your legs and don't move!
"Go, go, go!"
- You all right?
- Right as rain.
Get your hands back on the back.
- Now!
- Easy, Rigsby.
Easy.
Jessica!
Well, looks like you had it wrong.
There was no envelope
on the mayor's desk.
You're gonna wanna see this.
There's nothing there
because you have it stuffed
inside your bulletproof vest.
- Excuse me?
- He killed Ginger Crosswhite
and he killed Amber Sutherland.
Arnold?
What possible reason could I have
to hurt those women?
Well, Ginger, I'm not so sure about yet,
but Amber...
she found out, didn't she?
You got your killer right there.
Yeah, and you were terrified
I was starting to believe him.
If he was telling the truth about what
time he came home that night...
Then the security footage
doesn't make sense.
What do you mean?
Well, it's unlikely the electric
company meddled with it.
You had access to the evidence
and you changed it.
Amber, the video expert, figured it out.
And then you killed her.
But what you didn't know
is she left a message
about what she found
on the mayor's desk.
There was no envelope.
Yes, there was...
'Cause I put it there.
Now let's see it.
Chief Nail, take off your vest.
Open it.
Read it out.
"Arrest me."
Okay.
Look at that, huh?
You don't have to say that twice.
- I'm not going to jail!
- Don't do it! Don't.
Stay down!
That was close.
"We have people looking
at the security footage right now."
It's only a matter of time
before they figure out what you did.
Now you're a cop
about to go into the system.
You do the math.
Ginger Crosswhite got herself killed.
I want you to understand that.
"We'd talked at City Hall.
She was not an innocent."
"She married down.
Anybody could see that..."
"I certainly could."
"It was clear as day
that she was unhappy."
"There was a connection
between us."
"Very powerful one.
At least, I felt there was."
"But she was gonna tell the world..."
"Like I assaulted her."
"Defiled..."
Like I was some disgusting...
"thing."
"Where'd you get
the video of Crosswhite?"
"I hacked into the security footage,
changed the time stamp."
I had Crosswhite cold.
And that idiot Rowley forgot
to file the warrant.
So Crosswhite walked...
and lived in a purgatory you created
for him until he met Amber.
And she figured out that there was
something wrong with the footage?
Said the "meta-data" didn't match.
She had no idea I was involved.
And she said that she hadn't told
anyone else, so...
I met her at her home.
And you took her cameras
and you planted one at Crosswhite's.
In for a penny.
I thought that...
When I confessed, I would
feel a weight lift.
I don't feel anything.
Crosswhite.
It's time.
Hey...
Sorry about the whole jail thing
but you did take a bunch
of people hostage.
I don't care.
Jail doesn't mean anything to me now.
Yeah, well, see how you feel
about that in a couple years.
I'll be fine.
I can breathe again.
Thank you.
Are you familiar with the regulations
regarding agents giving anonymous
statements to the press?
CBI employees shall not give
anonymous
or "off the record" statements
to members of the media.
And what are the repercussions
of said violation?
- Suspension or termination.
- Yes.
However, both the Bagshaws are happy.
Everyone's alive.
We caught the killer.
Yes, sir.
See, you, you find the right lever
agent, you can move the world.
You found the right lever.
That was a smart play.
I hope you stay smart.
What was that about?
Oh, it was just business.
What's that?
This, this is my speeding ticket
that I refuse to pay.
Well, I'm not paying it.
Well, then I guess no one's gonna pay.
I'll get Bertram to pay it.
- How are you gonna do that?
- I have my ways.
It's on your desk!